Descripiton:

Let's use the website "https://quotes.toscrape.com/", which provides a collection of quotes from famous authors. Your task is to write a Python script using a web scraping library (such as BeautifulSoup or Scrapy) to extract quotes and authors from this website.

Here's your task:

Write a Python script to scrape quotes from the website "https://quotes.toscrape.com/". Your script should extract the text of each quote along with the name of the author. Print the extracted quotes and authors to the console.
You can use any web scraping library you prefer (such as BeautifulSoup, Scrapy, or any other). If you're not familiar with web scraping, you can start with BeautifulSoup, which is beginner-friendly.


Output from the code:

author: Albert Einstein - quote: “The world as we have created it is a process of our thinking. It cannot be changed without changing our thinking.”
author: J.K. Rowling - quote: “It is our choices, Harry, that show what we truly are, far more than our abilities.”
author: Jane Austen - quote: “The person, be it gentleman or lady, who has not pleasure in a good novel, must be intolerably stupid.”
author: Marilyn Monroe - quote: “Imperfection is beauty, madness is genius and it's better to be absolutely ridiculous than absolutely boring.”
author: André Gide - quote: “It is better to be hated for what you are than to be loved for what you are not.”
author: Thomas A. Edison - quote: “I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work.”
author: Eleanor Roosevelt - quote: “A woman is like a tea bag; you never know how strong it is until it's in hot water.”
author: Steve Martin - quote: “A day without sunshine is like, you know, night.” 